<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Noel the Spark</title>
    <description>NTS Electrical Services. Are you in need of a time served 24hr Emergency Electrician in Newtownabbey? For a full range of electrical services call us now.</description>
    <link>http://www.noelthespark.co.uk/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.noelthespark.co.uk/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Home</title>
        <description>&lt;h1&gt;NTS Electrical Services Belfast, Northern Ireland&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;24hr Emergency Electrician in Newtownabbey&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Noel The Spark is NTS&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NTS Electrical Services also known as `Noel the spark` as heard on Johnny Hero’s show on U105FM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here at NTS some of the work carried out by us on a monthly cycle would be grant work, we also carry out domestic electrical servicing as well as commercial. We are qualified electrical&amp;nbsp;contractors based in Newtownabbey and always work to the highest standards at all times. Noel O’Hare is not just a man who connects a few wires and hopes your lights work, he is a time served electrician with over 35 year’s experience. He will always work to the best of his abilities in order to provide you with a service that you would expect and works to the highest standard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don’t trust your home or business to just anybody; we hold the highest safety standards within this industry. Trust in our company goes a long way.&amp;nbsp; Time and time again past clients are prepared to wait a short time until we are free to do their jobs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re looking to have a kitchen rewired, a garage turned into an office, an outside light for your back garden or lights on your driveway, we can call for a visit to discuss your needs. We only advise but the final decisions will always be yours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our speciality is in that we personalise every job to each client. We pride ourselves in our approach to each job. We believe in keeping it clean and tidy. We clear up after each day so you don’t have to worry about that mess following you around your house or business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In brief, you should know the following about us: we are one of the longest established electrical contractors in Glengormley.&amp;nbsp; Our company was established in 1994 and has been responsible for providing outstanding electrical service ever since. We put our customers 1st all the time &amp;amp; we provide a 24/7 call out service. Our speciality is in that we personalise every job to each client.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We only use the best of materials &amp;amp; equipment. Don&#39;t you settle for anything less.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our regular customers particularly value our friendly service and that we are always at the end of a phone in time of need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our business is located at 27 Carnmoney Road Newtownabbey, BT36 6HL.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Services we provide:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/installation-and-maintenance&quot;&gt;Installation &amp;amp; Maintenance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/lighting&quot;&gt;Lighting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/alarm-systems&quot;&gt;Alarm Systems&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/consulting&quot;&gt;Consulting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/electrical-testing&quot;&gt;Electrical Testing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Contact us&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whenever or wherever you need help with your electrical problems, Noel is only a phone call away on the number displayed on this page.&amp;nbsp; Alternatively you can email us via the link from our “&lt;a title=&quot;Contact Us Page&quot; href=&quot;/contact-us&quot;&gt;Contact us&lt;/a&gt;” page.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.noelthespark.co.uk/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.noelthespark.co.uk/index.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Installation &amp;amp; Maintenance</title>
        <description>&lt;h1&gt;Electrical Services in Belfast&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We like to think of ourselves as your one stop shop for all your electrical requirements whether you are a homeowner, landlord, managing agent or business. We offer a great service to all our customers and carry out electrical works to a high standard no matter how big or small the job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is a list of the electrical services we offer to both domestic &amp;amp; commercial customers in Belfast and the surrounding areas including Newtownabbey, Carrickfergus and Newtownards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Electrical Services&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Lighting and power installations&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Fire alarm and emergency lighting systems&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Data and telephone systems&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;CCTV installations&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Flood lighting installations&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Factory maintenance&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Full Electrical Testing Services&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Electrical maintenance services&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Portable appliance testing&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Fire alarm Testing&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Emergency Lighting Testing&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;All Aspects of Electrical testing&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We offer a 24hr emergency service so you have no need to worry about calling us outside normal working hours.&amp;nbsp; You can rely on us to be there whenever and wherever we are needed.&amp;nbsp; &lt;a title=&quot;Contact Us Page&quot; href=&quot;http://www.ntselectricalservices.com/contact-us&quot;&gt;Call us&lt;/a&gt; today for further information on our range of electrical services.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.noelthespark.co.uk/installation-and-maintenance</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.noelthespark.co.uk/installation-and-maintenance</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lighting</title>
        <description>&lt;h1&gt;Lighting &amp;amp; Design in Carrickfergus&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NTS Electrical Services offers a complete electrical service for domestic and commercial clients in Carrickfergus and the surrounding area including Belfast, Newtownabbey and Newtownards.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;Get in touch with us today for:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;  
&lt;li&gt;Fuse boards &amp;amp; consumer units&lt;/li&gt;  
&lt;li&gt;Rewiring and wiring installations&lt;/li&gt;  
&lt;li&gt;Security lighting and alarms&lt;/li&gt;  
&lt;li&gt;Periodic testing and inspection&lt;/li&gt;  
&lt;li&gt;Portable Appliance Testing (PAT testing)&lt;/li&gt;  
&lt;li&gt;Telephone wiring (extra BT points)&lt;/li&gt;  
&lt;li&gt;Emergency lighting&lt;/li&gt;  
&lt;li&gt;Internal and external lighting&lt;/li&gt;  
&lt;li&gt;Electrical work for new buildings&lt;/li&gt;  
&lt;li&gt;Extra socket outlets&lt;/li&gt;  
&lt;li&gt;Specialist lighting (touch sensitive dimming)&lt;/li&gt;  
&lt;li&gt;Garden lighting&lt;/li&gt;  
&lt;li&gt;Driveway lighting&lt;/li&gt;  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are extremely proud of the reputation we have acquired for our professional approach and quality of service.&amp;nbsp; Much of our business is derived from repeat customers and referrals.&amp;nbsp; We would love to add you to our list of clients – so for all your electrical requirements make NTS your first choice.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; You can contact us on the number displayed on this page or email using the link from our “&lt;a href=&quot;/contact-us&quot;&gt;Contact us&lt;/a&gt;” page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.noelthespark.co.uk/lighting</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.noelthespark.co.uk/lighting</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alarm Systems</title>
        <description>&lt;h1&gt;Alarm Systems in Belfast&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Alarm02&quot; src=&quot;/images/Alarm02.jpg&quot; width=&quot;105&quot; height=&quot;140&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; style=&quot;padding: 0px;&quot; /&gt; &lt;img alt=&quot;Alarm03&quot; src=&quot;/images/Alarm03.jpg&quot; width=&quot;105&quot; height=&quot;140&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; style=&quot;padding: 0px;&quot; /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;img alt=&quot;Alarm01&quot; src=&quot;/images/Alarm01.jpg&quot; width=&quot;178&quot; height=&quot;140&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; style=&quot;padding: 0px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can help you select the right security equipment for you!&lt;br /&gt;One alarm system might look like another but with many years of experience we can provide the knowledge for you to make the correct choice for your house or premises.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This system is for a customer who wanted a basic alarm for her daughter’s house. The beauty about the alarms we fit is they can be tailored from a basic system to a monitored intruder alarm system or whatever suits your needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keypads can be fitted at the entry / exit point. Or you can have another keypad fitted on your landing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The three pictures show panel being wired, keypad being programmed and the keypad closed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We cover Newtownabbey and the Greater Belfast areas so if you are considering installing an alarm system take advantage of our expertise.&amp;nbsp; Call us now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  

	
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.noelthespark.co.uk/alarm-systems</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.noelthespark.co.uk/alarm-systems</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Consulting</title>
        <description>&lt;h1&gt;Electrical Contractor in Carrickfergus&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Ask Noel The Spark&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Does using the blow dryer in the bedroom cause the light in the hallway to flicker?&amp;nbsp; Has one of your light fixtures been burning through bulbs faster than you can say “don’t turn that light on”?&amp;nbsp; Well, it might be time for you to call the professionals at &lt;strong&gt;NTS&lt;/strong&gt; and let their expertise and experience go to work for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NTS&lt;/strong&gt; offers comprehensive electrical contracting services at rates that won’t short circuit your bank account. Our experienced, helpful electricians can take care of all those electrical repairs that you desperately need and can even give you pointers on upgrades that can make a world of difference without costing a pretty penny.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even the most adept do-it-yourself handyman sometimes needs a little help from a professional. If you are looking for some expert troubleshooting assistance for a nagging electrical problem, we hope you will think of Noel The Spark. Our team can handle all your electrical work, regardless of the size of the job or the degree of difficulty involved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our team have an excellent reputation in Carrickfergus and throughout the greater Belfast areas.&amp;nbsp; Call us today to see what we have to offer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.noelthespark.co.uk/consulting</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.noelthespark.co.uk/consulting</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Electrical Testing</title>
        <description>&lt;h1&gt;Electrical Testing in the Greater Belfast areas&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;EICR Testing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An EICR or Electrical Condition Report will show the condition of the electrical wiring in a property and checks the safety of the electrical installation. This type of electrical testing is carried out every five years in a commercial building and ten years in a domestic property, however this does depend on the age and condition of the installation that is being tested.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of our fully qualified electricians will attend your property when convenient for you and carry out 100% testing where possible. Upon completion of testing an NICEIC certificate will be issued and sent to you for your records.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Should anything fail then we will let you know on your certificate why it has failed and issue a recommendation sheet and include a free no obligation quote for your consideration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;P.A.T. Testing&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may have heard this type of testing referred to as PAT testing. This type of testing is a vital part of your Health and Safety requirements in the workplace and is a form of electrical safety testing to establish how safe the electrical items you use on a day to day basis. This can be anything from a computer, kettle or fan in your workplace and we can even carry out a microwave admissions safety test at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Health and Safety at Work Act 1974 puts the duty of care upon both the employer and the employee to ensure the safety of all persons using the work premises, this also includes the self employed. There are guidelines regarding how often an item of electrical equipment should be tested but HSE Guidance Notes advise &quot;regular testing&quot; which is generally interpreted as annual testing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This of course does depends on a number of different factors such as the age and type of equipment and if you have moved or introduced new items like a laptop in between your last test.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PAT Testing is required if you rent a property.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Get in touch&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regular electrical testing can prevent a fire in your home or property and potentially save lives.&amp;nbsp; If you are unsure if you require it give us a call as soon as possible on the number displayed on this page.&amp;nbsp; Alternatively you can email via the link from our “&lt;a href=&quot;/contact-us&quot;&gt;Contact us&lt;/a&gt;” page and we will contact you as a matter of urgency.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.noelthespark.co.uk/electrical-testing-electrician-newtownabbey</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.noelthespark.co.uk/electrical-testing-electrician-newtownabbey</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>About us - Noel The Spark</title>
        <description>&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Us - NTS Electrical Services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 style=&quot;margin-bottom: 20pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Electricians you can rely on&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 style=&quot;margin-bottom: 20pt; text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;&lt;inline style=&quot;color: #262626;&quot;&gt;NTS Electrical Services provides the highest quality service for a wide range of electrical work, which includes:&lt;/inline&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Industrial electrical maintenance and installation&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Commercial and domestic electrical maintenance and installation&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;New houses and alterations / renovations&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CCTV &amp;amp; Alarm Systems&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;inline style=&quot;color: #262626;&quot;&gt;NTS Electrical Services has an experienced team who are committed to providing an efficient and reliable service to you every time. &lt;/inline&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;inline style=&quot;color: #262626;&quot;&gt;Contact us for a free quote. &lt;a onclick=&quot;window.open(this.href,&#39;&#39;,&#39;scrollbars=yes,resizable=yes,location=yes,menubar=yes,status=yes,toolbar=yes,left=0,top=0&#39;);return false;&quot; href=&quot;/contact-us&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enquiry Link&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/inline&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;inline style=&quot;color: #262626;&quot;&gt;Over the past twenty years NTS Electrical Services has successfully undertaken a number of major industrial and commercial projects. NTS Electrical Services has all the current certificates &amp;amp; hold Public Liability Insurance (PLI).&lt;/inline&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Customers come to Noel The Spark as he is known to many people because ‘Noel The Spark Electrical Services offers technical expertise in electrical contracting and extreme customer satisfaction.&amp;nbsp; At NTSES, we have been working hard for our clients since 1994, and are a fully paid up members of the NICEIC approved contractors. Noel The Spark is also on the electrical safety register governed by ELECSA, NICEIC &amp;amp; ECA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NTS Electrical Services is one of the longest established electrical contracting company’s in Glengormley, Newtownabbey, Belfast, Northern Ireland.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can help you with electrical testing, led lighting, alarm systems and consulting in Glengormley, Belfast, Northern Ireland,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contact NTS Electrical Services today.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.noelthespark.co.uk/about-us-electrician-newtownabbey-nts-electrical-services-belfast-spark</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.noelthespark.co.uk/about-us-electrician-newtownabbey-nts-electrical-services-belfast-spark</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Contact us</title>
        <description>&lt;div style=&quot;display:none; !Important&quot;&gt;
	_
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Contact us&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	Please contact us on:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
	07889 119672
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	27 Carnmoney Road&lt;br&gt;
	 Glengormley
	&lt;br&gt;Belfast
	&lt;br&gt;Antrim
	&lt;br&gt;BT36 6HL&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;link href=&quot;/css/contact.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot; type=&quot;text/css&quot;&gt;

&lt;!--
&lt;form id=&quot;069f5be5contact&quot; class=&quot;contact_module_form&quot; onsubmit=&quot;return validator.init(this)&quot; name=&quot;contact&quot; action=&quot;&quot; method=&quot;post&quot; data-prefix=&quot;069f5be5&quot;&gt;
    		 			 &lt;input type=&quot;hidden&quot; name=&quot;contact_form&quot; value=&quot;1486&quot;&gt;
    			 &lt;input type=&quot;hidden&quot; name=&quot;capatcha&quot; value=&quot;1&quot;&gt;
    			 &lt;div class=&quot;fieldHolder&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;fieldLabel&quot;&gt;
    			 	 	 Name
    			 	 &lt;/div&gt;
    			 	 &lt;input class=&quot;formInput&quot; type=&quot;text&quot; placeholder=&quot;Name&quot; id=&quot;069f5be5Name&quot; alt=&quot;Name:::Name&quot; name=&quot;Name&quot; data-secret=&quot;TmFtZTo6Ok5hbWU=&quot; size=&quot;118&quot; maxlength=&quot;250&quot; value=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    		 		 &lt;span class=&quot;validation&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    		 	 &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;fieldHolder&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;fieldLabel&quot;&gt;
    			 	 	 Phone
    			 	 &lt;/div&gt;
    			 	 &lt;input class=&quot;formInput&quot; type=&quot;text&quot; placeholder=&quot;Phone&quot; id=&quot;069f5be5Phone&quot; alt=&quot;Numbers:::Phone&quot; name=&quot;Phone&quot; data-secret=&quot;TnVtYmVyczo6OlBob25l&quot; size=&quot;118&quot; maxlength=&quot;250&quot; value=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    		 		 &lt;span class=&quot;validation&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    		 	 &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;fieldHolder&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;fieldLabel&quot;&gt;
    			 	 	 Email
    			 	 &lt;/div&gt;
    			 	 &lt;input class=&quot;formInput&quot; type=&quot;text&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email&quot; id=&quot;069f5be5Email&quot; alt=&quot;Email:::Email&quot; name=&quot;Email&quot; data-secret=&quot;RW1haWw6OjpFbWFpbA==&quot; size=&quot;118&quot; maxlength=&quot;250&quot; value=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    		 		 &lt;span class=&quot;validation&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    		 	 &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;fieldHolder&quot; style=&quot;width: 100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;fieldLabel&quot;&gt;
    		 	 	 	 Details
    		 	 	 &lt;/div&gt;
    		 	 	 &lt;textarea class=&quot;formTextarea&quot; type=&quot;text&quot; placeholder=&quot;Details&quot; name=&quot;Details&quot; id=&quot;069f5be5Details&quot; alt=&quot;None:::Details&quot; data-secret=&quot;Tm9uZTo6OkRldGFpbHM=&quot; rows=&quot;5&quot;&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;
    		 		 &lt;span class=&quot;validation&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    		 	 &lt;/div&gt;			 &lt;!--&lt;br style=&quot;clear:both;&quot; /&gt; --&gt;
    			&lt;!-- &lt;input type=&quot;hidden&quot; name=&quot;3691ab5a62643073240910961aec5098&quot; value=&quot;1&quot;&gt;
    						 &lt;div id=&quot;recaptcha_widget&quot; class=&quot; recaptcha_nothad_incorrect_sol recaptcha_isnot_showing_audio&quot;&gt;
    						     &lt;div style=&quot;width: auto; overflow: hidden; margin: 0px auto 10px; clear: both; text-align: center; display: block; box-shadow: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.2) 0px 0px 5px inset; border: 1px solid rgb(180, 180, 180); padding: 10px; border-radius: 5px; height: auto; background: white;&quot; id=&quot;recaptcha_image&quot;&gt;&lt;img id=&quot;recaptcha_challenge_image&quot; alt=&quot;reCAPTCHA challenge image&quot; height=&quot;57&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; src=&quot;http://www.google.com/recaptcha/api/image?c=03AHJ_VuvlhWF0tJES6XvGSy8nxHSVR3SrdOP4GmXGsbcH2X4W4JU_Fw41vx7S454PwSf13LYp10fdP1WhEg7aIsfzhvwRbliFokpRKrsyglRoiyWBPnzXkNrljBkEiz2TCwjmlP-qGenXVIDB2L66d4xIF813ymrq041c8wOgvmYH9pziqimFamLthLa93g7c4p3UoHmHZWLqLhTp3BSitiX4mX3EqqMR_3h9Rs5TdeZwn9Y1EfFqQrMh5D5aBHq1fcmJGq4CwnBiKVdNtT0Yp4y9lBuAdf6plv520k77QG2aeBuLH6alY-U&amp;amp;th=,8f0ABB4AEo_4ADcrZ0yAGc4L3ceMNL-zHEH8siTY9s6nlyjkva9XtMSVZMf1dtDf5qqGFjbgfMei5es8Pnn-YkBb2ABPbGCZBdjgIepforjELFQ8i_bbb8MHnQOmFtdJ-G4x3GJi-kuJXnP6ep6umFTLBNTmfqJtA3tFjGQ9OgpvLG6y-a0dZgVC1qxyFQVor4TI3A&quot; style=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    						     &lt;div class=&quot;recaptcha_only_if_incorrect_sol&quot; style=&quot;color:red&quot;&gt;Incorrect please try again&lt;/div&gt;
    						     &lt;span class=&quot;recaptcha_only_if_image&quot;&gt;Enter the words above:&lt;/span&gt;
    						     &lt;span class=&quot;recaptcha_only_if_audio&quot;&gt;Enter the numbers you hear:&lt;/span&gt;
    						     &lt;span id=&quot;recaptcha_challenge_field_holder&quot; style=&quot;display: none;&quot;&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;hidden&quot; name=&quot;recaptcha_challenge_field&quot; id=&quot;recaptcha_challenge_field&quot; value=&quot;03AHJ_VuvlhWF0tJES6XvGSy8nxHSVR3SrdOP4GmXGsbcH2X4W4JU_Fw41vx7S454PwSf13LYp10fdP1WhEg7aIsfzhvwRbliFokpRKrsyglRoiyWBPnzXkNrljBkEiz2TCwjmlP-qGenXVIDB2L66d4xIF813ymrq041c8wOgvmYH9pziqimFamLthLa93g7c4p3UoHmHZWLqLhTp3BSitiX4mX3EqqMR_3h9Rs5TdeZwn9Y1EfFqQrMh5D5aBHq1fcmJGq4CwnBiKVdNtT0Yp4y9lBuAdf6plv520k77QG2aeBuLH6alY-U&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;text&quot; id=&quot;recaptcha_response_field&quot; name=&quot;recaptcha_response_field&quot; placeholder=&quot;Captcha&quot; autocomplete=&quot;off&quot; style=&quot;margin: 0px auto; width: 100%; text-align: center; text-indent: 0px;&quot;&gt;
    						     &lt;div class=&quot;recapControls&quot;&gt;
    							     &lt;div class=&quot;recaptcha_new&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;javascript:Recaptcha.reload()&quot; title=&quot;Get another CAPTCHA&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    							     &lt;div class=&quot;recaptcha_only_if_image&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;javascript:Recaptcha.switch_type(&#39;audio&#39;)&quot; title=&quot;Get an audio CAPTCHA&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    							     &lt;div class=&quot;recaptcha_only_if_audio&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;javascript:Recaptcha.switch_type(&#39;image&#39;)&quot; title=&quot;Get an image CAPTCHA&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    							     &lt;div class=&quot;recaptcha_help&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;javascript:Recaptcha.showhelp()&quot; title=&quot;Show Help&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    						     &lt;/div&gt;
    						 &lt;/div&gt;
    						 &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot; src=&quot;http://www.google.com/recaptcha/api/challenge?k=6LcjkNcSAAAAAE7UVDLDC6mUOURRZEYwLOb2-3dn&quot;&gt;
    						 &lt;/script&gt;&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot; src=&quot;http://www.google.com/recaptcha/api/js/recaptcha.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
    						 &lt;noscript&gt;
    						     &amp;lt;iframe src=&quot;http://www.google.com/recaptcha/api/noscript?k=6LcjkNcSAAAAAE7UVDLDC6mUOURRZEYwLOb2-3dn&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; width=&quot;500&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/iframe&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
    						     &amp;lt;textarea name=&quot;recaptcha_challenge_field&quot; rows=&quot;3&quot; cols=&quot;40&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/textarea&amp;gt;
    						     &amp;lt;input type=&quot;hidden&quot; name=&quot;recaptcha_response_field&quot; value=&quot;manual_challenge&quot;&amp;gt;
    						 &lt;/noscript&gt;
    
    				  	 			  &lt;div&gt;
    			 			 	 &lt;input class=&quot;formButton contact_form_button&quot; align=&quot;right&quot; type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Send &gt;&quot; name=&quot;formSubmit&quot; style=&quot;width: 100%; padding: 8px 10px; text-shadow: none; border: none; font-weight: bold; font-size: 16px; background-color: rgb(0, 0, 0);&quot;&gt;
    			 			 &lt;/div&gt;
    		 &lt;/form&gt; --&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.noelthespark.co.uk/contact-us</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.noelthespark.co.uk/contact-us</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
